Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Merrick David vs Actors Equity Association; Metal Specialties Products Corp. vs IBT Local 295, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Issue: Rates of pay - contract interpretation; discipline - discharge - negligence and carelessness.
- Metropolitan Correctional Center vs American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), Council of Prison Local, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - negligence and carelessness. (Award Only).
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. vs Insurance Workers of America; Metropolitan Museum of Art vs American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1503, 1958-1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - dual employment - plant; rates of pay - overtime. (Award Only.)
- Mid-Atlantic Packaging and Specialties, Inc. vs UPIU Local 375; Mid-Penn Telephone Co vs Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Local 103, 1977- 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Issue: Layoff - demotion; call-in - seniority. (Award Only.)
- Midwest Steel Co. vs USA Local 6103, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  Issue: Schedules of work - change of schedule; absences - tardiness; vacancies - temporary - seniority. (Award Only.)
- Midwest Steel Co. vs USA Local 6103, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - excessive absences. TR, RC, B, EX, AN.
- Midwest Steel Co. vs USA Local 6103, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Miles Shoes, Inc. vs RWDSU District 65; Milwaukee Newspapers, Inc. vs Milwaukee Newspaper and Graphic Communications Union No 23, 1960-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - unsatisfactory work, tardiness; assignment of jobs - workload. (Award Only.)
- Mobil Oil Corp vs OCAW Local 8-801, Local 8-831; Montgomery Ward vs RWDSU Local 590; Murray Co of Texas, Inc. vs USA Local 4335, 1963-1976 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Issue: Rates of pay - overtime; discipline - discharge - unsatisfactory work, excessive absences; discipline - discharge - theft, company property; rates of pay - vacation pay, layoff. (Award Only.)
- National Cash Register Corp vs IAM Local 1607; Nabisco, Inc. vs International Bakery and Confectionery Workers Local 492, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  Issue: Sub-contracting - janitorial work; recall - seniority; discipline - suspension - improper job attitude. (Award Only.)
- National Basketball Association (NBA) vs. California Sports, Inc., Lakers, (Wilt Chamberlain), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  Issue: Contract interpretation. TR, RC, B, EX, AN, SD.
- National Basketball Association (NBA) vs. California Sports, Inc., Lakers, (Wilt Chamberlain), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- National Basketball Association (NBA) vs. California Sports, Inc., Lakers, (Wilt Chamberlain), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- National Basketball Association (NBA) vs. California Sports, Inc., Lakers, (Wilt Chamberlain), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- NBA - Baltimore Bullets Basketball Club, Inc. vs. Archie L. Clark, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Issue: Contracts - binding effect. AN, RC, SD, EX, B.
- NBA - Baltimore Bullets Basketball Club, Inc. vs. Archie L. Clark, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- NBA vs. National Basketball Players' Association (NBPA), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  Issue: Contracts - past practice; contract silence. TR, RC, B, SD, EX, AN.
- NBA vs. National Basketball Players' Association (NBPA), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- NBA vs. National Basketball Players' Association (NBPA), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- NBA - Houston Rockets vs. NBPA, John S. Valley, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  Issue: Fringe benefits - pension - eligibility; rates of pay - severance pay. RC, AN, SD.
- NBA - Seattle Supersonics vs. NBPA, John Brisker, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation; assignment of jobs. SD, RC, B, Agreement.
- NBA - Chicago Professional Sports Corp., Chicago Bulls vs. NBPA, Robert E. Love, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Issue: Contract modification - wage adjustments; absences. RC, B, AN, SD, EX.
- NBA - Chicago Professional Sports Corp., Chicago Bulls vs. NBPA, Robert E. Love, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- NBA - Chicago Professional Sports Corp., Chicago Bulls vs. NBPA, Robert E. Love, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- NBA - Pro Basketball, Inc., Portland Trail Blazers vs. NBPA, Bob Davis, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - termination of employment - rates of pay. RC, SD, AN, EX, B.
- NBA - Pro Basketball, Inc., Portland Trail Blazers vs. NBPA, Bob Davis, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- NBA - Pro Basketball, Inc., Portland Trail Blazers vs. NBPA, Bob Davis, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- NBA - Pro Basketball, Inc., Portland Trail Blazers vs. NBPA, Bob Davis, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- NBA - New Orleans Basketball Clubs vs. NBPA, Toby Kimball, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - termination of employment - rates of pay. TR, RC, AN, EX, B.
- NBA - New Orleans Basketball Clubs vs. NBPA, Toby Kimball, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- NBA - New Orleans Basketball Clubs vs. NBPA, Toby Kimball, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- NBA - New Orleans Basketball Clubs vs. NBPA, Toby Kimball, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- NBA - Supersonics vs. NBPA, John Brisker, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Settled. RC, B, LD, SD.
- NBA - Boston Celtics Basketball Club, Inc. vs. NBPA, Paul Silas, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - inconsistent provision - intent. TR, EX, RC, B, SD, AN.
- NBA - Boston Celtics Basketball Club, Inc. vs. NBPA, Paul Silas, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Issue: Fringe benefits - meal allowances. RC, B, SD, AN.
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15a)
  Issue: Schedules of wok - time off schedules. (Award only).
- NBA vs. NBPA, California Summer League, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Issue: Contract interpretation. RC, SD, B.
- Zelmo Beatty vs. Mountain States Sports, Utah Stars, and Bill Daniels, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - rates of pay - back-pay awards. TR, RC, SD, AN.
- NBA - Indiana Pacers vs. NBPA, Darrell Elston, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Issue: Rates of pay - disability. RC, B, AN, SD.
- NBA - Atlanta Hawks vs. NBPA, Bill Willoughby, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Issue: Discipline - off-duty conduct. RC, AN, SD.
- NBA - Denver Nuggets vs. NBPA, Rudy Hackett, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  Issue: Rates of pay. RC, B, SD, AN.
- NBA - Denver Nuggets vs. NBPA, Rudy Hackett, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- NBA - Cincinnati Basketball Club Co. and Kings Professional Basketball Club vs. NBPA, Darrall Imhoff, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Issue: Termination of Employment - disability - contract interpretation. RC, B, SD, EX.
- NBA - Cincinnati Basketball Club Co. and Kings Professional Basketball Club vs. NBPA, Darrall Imhoff, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- NBA vs. NBPA, Leonard Robinson, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Issue: Contracts - contract interpretation. RC, B, AN, SD.
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Issue: Contract interpretation. TR, RC, B, AN, SD, EX.
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- NBA vs. NBPA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- NBA vs. NBPA (Chicago Club), Chester Walker, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Issue: Timeliness - appeal to arbitration. (Award only).
- NBA vs. NBPA, Paul Silas, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Issue: Rates of pay - transfer. RC, AN, B.
- NBA, New Jersey Nets vs. NBPA, David Wohl, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Issue: Rates of pay - transfer. AN, RC, B.
- NBA (New Jersey Nets) vs. NBPA (Jim Eakins), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Issue: Rates of pay - transfers.
- NBA - Chicago Club vs. NBPA, Chester Walker, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; employees' rights - transfer of work. TR, RC, EX, B, SD, EX.
- NBA - Chicago Club vs. NBPA, Chester Walker, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- NBA - Chicago Club vs. NBPA, Chester Walker, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- NBA - Denver Nuggets vs. NBPA, Brian Taylor, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Issue: Compensation - rates of pay. SD, AN, EX, RC, B.
- NBA - Denver Nuggets vs. NBPA, Brian Taylor, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- NBA - Seattle Supersonics vs. NBPA, Gerald Edwards, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Issue: Termination of Employment - disability - rates of pay. TR, SD, EX, AN, RC, B.
- NBA - Seattle Supersonics vs. NBPA, Gerald Edwards, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- NBA - Seattle Supersonics vs. NBPA, Gerald Edwards, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- NBA - Atlanta Hawks vs. NBPA, Michael Sojourner, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Issue: Suspension - disability - compensation. RC, B, AN, TR, EX, SD.
- NBA - Atlanta Hawks vs. NBPA, Michael Sojourner, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- NBA - Atlanta Hawks vs. NBPA, Michael Sojourner, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- NBA - Chicago Bulls vs. NBPA, Leon Benbow, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Issue: Disability - benefits. RC, B, TR, AN, SD.
- NBA - Chicago Bulls vs. NBPA, Leon Benbow, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- NBA - Atlanta Hawks vs. NBPA, Ken Charles, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Issue: Termination of employment - contract interpretation. RC, B, SD, AN, EX.
- NBA - Golden State Warriors vs. NBPA, Charles Johnson, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Issue: Rates of pay - change in contracts. RC, B, AN, SD.
- NBA - Detroit Pistons vs. National Basketball Players Association, Ben Poquette, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Issue: Timeliness - delay in filing grievance; contract interpretation. RC, B, AN, EX.
- NBA - Cleveland Professional Basketball Co. vs. NBPA, Ronald Cox, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Issue: Rates of pay - disability - contract interpretation. RC, B, SD, AN.
- National Broadcasting Company vs. International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE), Local 771, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - jurisdiction - assignment of jobs. AN, RC, B, EX.
- National Fuel Gas Distribution Corp. vs IBEW Local 2199, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive - tardiness; rates of pay - incentive pay. (Award Only.)
- National Standard co., Worcester Wire Works Division vs USA Local 2865; National Starch and Chemical Corp vs International Printing and Graphic Communications Union Local 474; National Sugar Refining Co vs Sugar Refinery Workers Local 1648, 1963-1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Issue: Rates of pay - incentive; assignment of jobs - seniority; discipline - layoff. (Award Only.)
- National Sugar Refining Co. vs United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers Local 580; vs Sugar Refining Workers Local 1648; New Brunswick Tool and Die Co vs IAM Local 47, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - insubordination; seniority - posting vacancies; discipline - demotion - unsatisfactory work. (Award Only.)
- New England Telephone and Telegraph Co. vs IBEW Local 2222, Local 2311-2327, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - application for employment - falsification - absences; assignment of jobs - management rights. (Award Only.)
- New England Telephone and Telegraph Co. vs IBEW Local 2222, Local 2320-27, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude; discipline - discharge - theft; discipline - discharge - plant rules - violation.
- New England Telephone and Telegraph Co. vs IBEW Local 2222, Local 2313, Local 2315, Local 2320-27, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Issue: Seniority, transfers. TR, EX, RC, B, SD.
- New England Telephone and Telegraph Co. vs IBEW Local 2222, Local 2313, Local 2315, Local 2320-27, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- New England Telephone and Telegraph Co. vs IBEW Local 2222, Local 2313, Local 2315, Local 2320-27, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- New Fairfield Board of Education vs New Fairfield Education Association; New Haven Board of Education vs New Haven Federation of Teachers Local 933, 1976- 1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification; discipline - leaving plant without permission. (Award Only.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Co. vs IBEW Local 827, 1960-1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - leaving plant without permission; rates of pay - guaranteed rate; grievance - timeliness. (Award Only.)
- New Rochell, City of vs Police Association of New Rochelle, Inc.; New York City, Office of Aging vs AFSCME Local 371; New York City vs Fire Alarm Dispatchers Benevolent Association; New York City Department of Health vs Doctors' Council, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Issue: Rates of pay - overtime; rates of pay - below contract rate; absences - illness - plant rules - past practice; rates of pay - differentials. (Award Only.)
- New York City Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. AFCSME, District Council 37, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Issue: Rates of pay - differential. TR, RC, B, EX, AN.
- New York City Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. AFCSME, District Council 37, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- New York City Department of Transportation vs. MEBA, District 1, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Issue: Rates of pay - overtime - holiday. TR, RC, EX, SD.
- New York City Department of Transportation vs. MEBA, District 1, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- New York City vs. Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, District 1, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Issue: Holidays; overtime; absences. TR, AN, EX, SD.
- New York City vs. Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, District 1, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Issue: Management rights - vacation rescheduling; rates of pay. (Award only).
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Issue: Schedules of work - change of schedule - overtime. TR, RC, B, AN, EX.
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Issue: Working conditions - use of personal automobile. (Award only).
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Hearings suspended. RC, B, EX, AN. (No award).
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolman's Benevolent Association, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- New York City vs. Social Service Employees Union, AFSCME, Local 371, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Settled. RC, SD, AN, B.
- New York City vs. Social Service Employees Union. AFSCME, Local 371, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercations. RC, AN, B, SD, EX.
- New York City vs. Social Service Employees Union. AFSCME, Local 371, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- New York City Department of Social Services vs Social Service Employees Union, AFSCME, Local 371, 1974-1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Issue: Suspension - fights and altercation; rates of pay - time not worked; rates of pay - adjustment; discipline - discharge - fights and altercations. (Award Only.)
- New York City Department of Social Services vs Social Service Employees Union, AFSCME, Local 371; New York City Human Resources Administration vs District Council 37, AFSCME and Social Service Employees Union Local 371, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - change in location; rates of pay - time not worked. (Award Only.)
- New York City Department of Social Services vs Social Service Employees Union, AFSCME, Local 371, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - classification of jobs; transfers - involuntary. (Award Only.)
- New York City Department of Social Services vs Social Service Employees Union, AFSCME, Local 371, 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude - general attitude; rates of pay - guaranteed rate; rates of pay - reclassification.
- New York City Department of Social Services vs Social Service Employees Union, AFSCME, Local 371, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - carelessness and negligence - insubordination; schedules of work; discipline - discharge - leaving work area without permission. (Award Only.)
- New York City Board of Education vs Council of Supervisors and Administrators of the City of New York; New York City Department of Buildings vs Allied Building Inspectors, International Union Operating Engineers (IUOE) Local 211, 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  Issue: Promotions - training and trial periods; grievance procedure - failure to follow; assignment of jobs - qualifications; assignment of jobs - discipline. (Award Only.)
- New York City Housing Authority vs International Union of Elevator Constructors Local 1; New York City Opera, Division of the City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. vs American Guild of Musical Artists, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Issue: Welfare fund - rules for operation of plan; fringe benefits - welfare fund; rates of pay - contracts - effective date. (Award Only).
- New York City Opera Co. vs. American Guild of Musical Artists, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Issue: Seniority - right to a job - assignment of jobs. RC, B, AN, EX.
- New York City Opera Co. vs. American Guild of Musical Artists, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- New York City Opera vs. American Guild of Musical Artists, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Settled. RC, EX, B.
- New York City Subway Advertising Co. vs. OPEIU, Local 153; New York City Transit Authority vs Patrolmens Benevolent Association New York City Transit Police Department, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge dishonesty; assignment of jobs - transfers. (Award only).
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Civil Service Technical Guild, AFSCME, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - job description. RC, B, EX, SD.
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Civil Service Technical Guild, AFSCME, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Civil Service Technical Guild, AFSCME, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - outside classification. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Transit Supervisors Organization, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. AN, B, RC, EX.
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Civil Service Technical Guild, AFSCME, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Issue: Promotion - effect on wage progression. RC, B, AN, EX, SD.
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Civil Service Technical Guild, AFSCME, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Civil Service Technical Guild, AFSCME, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- New York Journal-American vs New York Mailers Union, Number 6 International Typographical Union (ITU); New York Post Corp vs Newspaper Guild of New York, American Newspaper Guild; vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, 1957-1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  Issue: Schedules of work - change of schedule; severance pay - voluntary quit; standards of production - failure to meet; reclassification - rates of pay. (Award Only.)
- New York Post Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Issue: Jurisdiction - supervisors - inclusion in bargaining unit. TR, AN, RC, B, EX, SD.
- New York Post Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- New York Post Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- New York Post Corp vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  RC only. (No award).
- New York Post Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - upgrading. TR, RC, B, AN, SD, EX.
- New York Post Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- New York Racing Association vs. Independent Association of Mutual Employees of New York State, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  Issue: Fringe benefits - pension plan. (Award only).
- New York Racing Association vs. IBEW, Local 3, Division of Mutual Employees, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Issue: Strikes. SD, B, Agreement, photographs.
- New York Telephone Co. vs Communication Workers of America (CWA) District 1; vs. CWA, Local 1123, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - disloyalty - verbal disrespect; discipline - discharge - absences - tardiness; discipline - discharge - alcoholism. (Award Only).
- New York Telephone Co. vs Communication Workers of America (CWA) Local 1111; vs. CWA Local 1129; vs. Telephone Traffic Union, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  Issue: Promotion - qualifications - seniority; discipline - discharge - theft. (Award Only.)
- New York Telephone Co. vs. Communications Workers of America, District 1, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules; disloyalty. RC, B, EX, SD, AN.
- New York Telephone Co. vs. Communications Workers of America, District 1, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- New York Telephone Co. vs. Communications Workers of America, District 1, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- New York Times Corp. vs Newspaper Guild of New York, 1957-1974 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - conviction of crime; rates of pay - holiday, overtime - increase, contract interpretation. (Award Only.)
- Newark Board of Education vs City Association of Supervisors and Administrators, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  Issue: Management rights - crew size; strikes - supervisors - starting time - change; rates of pay - promotion; schedules of work - assignment of jobs. (Award Only.)
- Newark Board of Education vs City Association of Supervisors and Administrators, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  Issue: Schedules of work - change in hours; promotions - transfers; promotion - eligibility. (Award Only.)
- Newark Board of Education vs. City Association of Supervisors and Administrators, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  Issue: Schedules of work - overtime. RC, B, AN.
- Newark Board of Education vs. City Association of Supervisors and Administrators, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Newark Board of Education vs. City Association of Supervisors and Administrators, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  Issue: Rates of pay - jury duty. RC, B, AN, EX.
- Newark Brush Co. vs Federal Labor Union Number 23759; Newark, City of vs. Fraternal Order, 1960-1981 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - strikes, slowdowns; layoff - recall. (Award Only.)
- Newark, City of vs. FOP, Lodge 12, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  Issue: Layoff - recall - seniority. RC, B, SD, EX, AN.
- Newark, City of vs. FOP, Lodge 12, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  Issue: Seniority - computation. RC, B, EX, AN, SD.
- Newark Morning Ledger Co vs ITU, Local 11, Newark Mailers Union; Newberry J.J., Co. vs IBT Local 852; New Syndicate Co. vs Newspaper Guild of New York; Newsday, Inc. vs ITU, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  Issue: Rates of pay - shift scheduling - overtime; discipline - discharge - alcoholism; discipline - tardiness; discipline - discharge - plant rules - improper personal conduct. (Award Only.)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory vs. Atomic Trades and Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Settled. RC, B, SD, AN.
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory vs. Atomic Trades and Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - promotion. RC, B, EX, AN.
- Oakville Co. vs UAW Local 1251; Ogden Food Service Corp. vs Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union Local 178; Oil Heat Engineering Co., Inc. vs IBT Local 553; Okonite Co. vs United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers (URW) Local 637, 1959-1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Issue: Subcontracting; discipline - discharge - plant rules; transfer - disciplinary; vacation pay; assignment of jobs - added duties. (Award Only.)